

CONTACT

Mianmujtabaasif1@gmail.com +92 304-6578361 Ali Town, Faisalabad, Pakistan

INTERESTS

Self-Learning

Traveling

E-Gaming

SKILLS

React JS

Node JS

Next JS

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

Database Management

PWA

AWS

CNC

API Integration



Personal Portfolio

MUJTABA ASIF

MERN FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Passionate and professional web developer with 2 years of experience with a sound knowledge of industry. Proficient of various technologies. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects as well as collaborate in a team setting.

EDUCATION

National Textile University, Faisalabad

BS Software Engineering 2018 - 2022

- Cumulative GPA of 2.6
- Member of the CS Society

Kips College, Faisalabad

F.Sc. Pre-Engineering 2014 - 2016

• Done intermediate with **A** grade

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Junior MERN Stack Developer

SMIT, Faisalabad 01/2020 - 09/2021

During my professional duration at SMIT I've developed, planned, tested, maintained, and deployed MERN web apps.

IT Consultant

Kay & Emms Pyt Ltd. Faisalabad 08/2017 - 06/2018

Collaborate with IT team to make ensure that everything perfect on employee computers.

COURSES

Presidential Initiative for Artificial Intelligence and Computing

Cloud Native Computing In Progress

SMIT, Faisalabad

MERN Stack Development 2017 - 2018

SMIT, Faisalabad

Web Designing 2016 - 2017

PROJECTS

In my professional 2 years as web developer I've learn much about latest web technologies and implemented my experience to done **20+** projects in **MERN** stack technology. Some of my developed projects details are mentioned below.

Technologies, Frameworks, and Libraries Used In Projects Are:

- React JS
- Express JS
- MongoDB / SQL
- Passport Local / JWT
- React Redux

- Context API
- ES6
- React Hooks
- Framer Motion
- JavaScript Libraries
- React Hooks
- Next JS
- Bootstrap
- Material UI
- Many others
- ✓ Authentication Based Textile Products Dispatching System As FYP
 My responsibility in project was to develop back-end using Express JS and documentation of project.
- ✓ E-Commerce Web Applications 8+
- ✓ Inventory Management Web Application 3+
- ✓ Custom Web Applications 10+

PERSONAL LINKS



github.com/MUJTABA1998/



profile-mujtaba-asif.herokuapp.com/